{
    "subject": "resource/Ibrahim_al-Jaafari",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Al-Hindiya",
    "human_readable": "Ibrahim al-Jaafari was born in Al-Hindiya.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9430409073829651,
            "question": "Where was Ibrahim al-Jaafari born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9251137971878052,
            "question": "When was Ibrahim al-Jaafari born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7135977745056152,
            "question": "What is Ibrahim al-Jaafari known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6219527125358582,
            "question": "In what country is Al-Hindiya located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5639213919639587,
            "question": "Name a prominent figure from Al-Hindiya."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5424277782440186,
            "question": "Who were some of Ibrahim al-Jaafari's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4515421390533447,
            "question": "What is the cultural significance of Al-Hindiya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4253738820552826,
            "question": "What are some significant events that occurred during Ibrahim al-Jaafari's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34574681520462036,
            "question": "What political positions has Ibrahim al-Jaafari held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2773289978504181,
            "question": "What impact did Ibrahim al-Jaafari have on Iraqi politics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ibrahim al-Jaafari was born in Al-Hindiya.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3588_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political positions has Ibrahim al-Jaafari held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3588_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some significant events that occurred during Ibrahim al-Jaafari's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3588_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the cultural significance of Al-Hindiya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3588_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3588_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents do not contain any information supporting the claim that Ibrahim al-Jaafari was born in Al-Hindiya. The provided texts mention that he was born in Karbala, which contradicts the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}